Welcome once again to the Main Toh Mari Fauj channel
friends, in this video I
want to discuss a very interesting question that was asked to me. The question that was asked in this video was that should we wait
for the next quarter to see how
119 fans come out before making fresh
investment. So I want to ask Rajput ji
whether we should wait till the next quarter i.e.
three more months. This result
season is going on, banks are also seen making provisioning for many companies, they are
showing it in their results by creating a separate section for provisioning, so they are saying that there are many
companies, take any sector, should we
wait till the next quarter's results too before we start investing pressure
because at this time two
voices are very much last meter, the first
thing is that the market is available at very cheap prices,
which are engaged, just like you go to the vegetable market and
buy vegetables, in the same
way at this time many companies are seen engaged in the stock market, there
are many companies at
very good prices  They are available and the
investor who has been following the market for a long time
sees that the company which
was worth Rs 2000 is definitely available for Rs 12, this company worth thousands
is definitely available for Rs 400-500, so from
within it is simple, simple, simple, simple, there is
speed, a simple trick, we
go to malls and see huge
discounts of 70-80 per cent, we see end of season sales,
these types of situations have been
created, so their question is
whether we should wait till the next quarter,
how does the liquid situation arise,
no, it is a very important question before investing,
I have raised this question long ago and
somewhere in the video, I will talk about it in two-three minutes,
I had
made a video, before that I must
tell you that I had
launched this pool, what type of
investor are you, whether you are a short term investor,
long term investor, intraday trader
So the reply of 56 percent people was
that they are long term investors, so I am
sharing this post with you because I just want to
share with you
at the market, even now the intraday investors have
shrunk to 20% these days, the short
term investors, that is those who buy and sell after
holding for a week or two or by
meeting together, have shrunk to 27%
and still around 55-60 percent, the
percentage of investors that is seen to be 60% of
long term investors is that
portfolios are still being built for the long term in the market, so this is
their question, this poll also has this
element somewhere, to show this poll that should we
keep the volume muted for fresh investment in the next quarter?
I think that the long term
investors are gradually
muting their portfolio every month, some
portfolio building, it does not have a three
month journey to define Manoj  It's a long
journey, and this heart always builds up. You keep
adding to your portfolio, you keep sending it with some money, you keep
building profits,
you keep taking out tight shares at the end so that it becomes
more lasting, you even
take out some shares at a very high profit, so everything keeps going on. So,
portfolio
building and liquidation of portfolio is a
continuous process, and it's a process. As long as
you are sitting in the market, people like Big Boss 7 portion, at that
time, people do the same thing like long-term interest,
and this is a
very big situation that I am also
building a portfolio for the next
five-six years, and what will happen in that too, is that
I am buying and selling stocks, so
later I keep adding some stocks every month, I am
building my portfolio
for the next
5-10 years, and this mindset is definitely there, but due to those
investors, these 27 percent
people, this is a situation of great confusion for them,
they look at the short-term indicators in the option market in the chart.
Somewhere, people are also engaged at this time
that they have to buy now, they have to sell now,
for them, what does a visit to Blackwater
mean in the next quarter, that
you are also going to change, yes, in options,
they are definitely writing on the call side
because they have to make money in the decline,
interpreters also, at this time, they even more
hold on to the Jhala candles, thinking, man,
what is this, they sell in the group that is going up, the
big question for those people is, for
long term investment,
we should start buying lightly, for long
term, bulk buying will
not be recommended at all, small
quantity, small amount, so
his answer was Jai Rajput, this is the time
for wholesale purchase, this is again the time for
very selective, very
muted quantity, it is the
time to purchase in very small quantities, I do
n't know right now, I get a good price in a helicopter,
I take the money, we should
not expect returns from the market in the next year,
now stories will come before us,
exceptional stories also  There will be a
story like Reliance, where did Reliance stock go as soon as Facebook investment came, there will be such
secret stories due to which we will
not have to be instruments, but the
broad index in front of us, I feel that at
this time the index is moving between 8000 to 9560,
in the next one year the same kind of index, as I
believe, it may keep
showing bottoms up to 8500, 8500 to 9500. This
day tax scope will remain till next year, so
we should not expect much return in this, this
price is not going to go away
for the long term and there are many very good
companies which will keep giving you good returns for the long term
in the coming days also,
so we do
not have to think of bulk buying at all,
secondly, which industries should be
our focus at this time,
which industries are to be avoided completely,
I made a video on Facebook ID
yesterday in which I told that for the first
time, which banks are profitable, what should be bought,
two confusions came out on that that
if these are for long-term  Let's
start with small quantities. 18 on that bed. S2
starts with a wearing certain qualities. Whether
it's an average of every kind, how much money is he
taking, he has thought of 50 stocks, but don't go for the
quantity. Set the same time
deposit in the world of rupees.
You can't bring that much money, make a deposit in thousands.
10,000 at a time on one stock.
More than that, I think this time should be done in
minutes. Now Attendant Amaze had definitely
said that whatever the length of a business is, it is
bad luck to lend money, whether it is a
bank or an investor, why did they leave, then
it should be folded. Some Lord and
Pierce is possible. In the coming time,
small UK launches say that we
want to share our portfolio. All the
finance companies that give money will
give more retail loans and less wholesale loans,
but SIM retail loans are also its thing.
Bajaj Finance System is on the back foot and is not
sharing details, although they have staff problems,
whatever the problems, but at this time,
whether it is wholesale entry  Whether it is a retail
loan provider, any company that is involved in
loan distribution business, we should avoid it at this time.
I have also reviewed many other stocks.
Praj Industries is a handset manufacturing
company. Companies of this type should
start writing accurately these
days, even if the situation is after 3 months,
if the vaccination does not come, then going
forward, more strict
guidelines will be seen and more
attractive social distancing messages will be seen.
This will directly impact consumer behavior.
Consumer means the
consumer who is buying the company's product. This is a
body. This is an insurance
company
that this kind of medical insurance, this
insurance business will be seen increasing.
Now see, it was discussed on Heroes Media
that what should be taken, if you go to the theater and
watch a movie, their business seems to be ruined for the next one
year. Engineers
India Limited was discussed on this,
construction work, do you think that
in the coming days too, there will be bread problem, if there is
finance problem, then construction
work  But what do you think, the contract was taken
that government construction projects will be done again,
so this is
Graphite India Limited, the company that gave the award,
Imitated the government has
not yet banned the import of its electrodes
which come from China, the
extra oil of graphite, so the fate of both these companies is
hanging in the balance.
Yes Bank of Graphite Kaur ji needs profitable results,
but it had not lifted a bond somewhere, she has
B.Ed.
Now our RBI is doing that, by taking its
results forward, the cylinder
business of these is also landing. Vodafone
provides the network, it is
getting rent properly, so at this time one will have to be very
selective.
I had made a video about Sterlite Technologies, that this
optical fiber business provides better networking,
nowadays work from home career has
started, so which is promoting this culture,
like Sterlite Technologies, it provides
basic infrastructure to provide you internet, the
company
makes official sites, which is praised,
so the future of these companies looks bright,
their demand is there.  It will grow and the world will have to deal with
Ashok Leyland Automobile Company
again, you really think this time it is a
company to buy, research is to transport goods from one place to another, if the
demand will decrease then for
a year the feature of such a company
was also a yagya, ₹50 is the stock, should you buy
again for long term start regulating
act Oxford time from bulk buying and
you should not have any side effects from these companies also,
some are turning 12 years old,
expect this in a five year career, there was
talk about leading banks, you have also
helped, Kotak Bank is also a bank, there is
talk about all the banking stocks,
then take a look at the prices, these prices are
not going anywhere, they will remain here, UPL which
manufactures the chemical used in making fertilizers for agriculture, it is a
good feature of them, the agriculture
industry is not going anywhere, these
facts and emphasis will be given on this,
we should maintain agriculture, so friends, at this
time the retail investor is definitely confused, but
if we use simple mathematics, simple logic  If we use it,
our investment will
definitely take a turn in smart management, so this is
my message in this video, friends, come,
you should understand what I want to say, still
if you have any question, please do
comment in the comment box, along with this, I want to
minor in the video, thank you so much for
watching,
tell me more.